Johanna Baguio

Web Developer

a 28-year old Filipina finding my way to the IT industry. I was lucky enough to be given the opportunity and be a graduate of Hack Your Future, where I was able to maximize the resources available for me to reach my maximum potential in both back-end and front-end development. I'm a fast- learner who embraces new challenges, while striving for competence and excellence. Join me as we explore endless possibilities in this rapidly changing world of technology.



Amsterdamvej 14, Copenhagen S, Denmark

f facebook.com/johbaguio

instagram.com/johbaguio

29642002

in linkedin.com/in/johanna-may-baguio-a8aa90174

github.com/johbaguio

EDUCATION

Dansk 2 CLAVIS

02/2019 - Present

Copenhagen, Denmark

Full Stack Web Development

Hack Your Future

08/2018 - 06/2019

Copenhagen, Denmark

Språk Kurs (A1,A2)

Folkeuniversitetet

01/2017 – 05/2017

Drammen, Norway

Bachelor of Science in Information and Communications Technology

University of San Carlos

06/2008 – 03/2013

Cebu, Philippines

WORK EXPERIENCE

Au Pair

Cultural Exchange Program

06/2018 – Present Copenhagen, Denmark

Contact: Martin Kaae Glarvig – +45 2323 2130

Au Pair

Cultural Exchange Program

01/2016 – 01/2018 Drammen, Norway

Contact: Vibeke Fredriksen – +47 902 01 933

Customer/Technical Service RepresentativeConvergys Philippines Incorporated

07/2013 - 01/2916

Cebu, Philippines

Achievements

- Sales Champion (May, June July, August 2015)
- Top Scorecard Achiever (January June 2015)
- Top Agent Year To Date (2015)
- Customer Service Excellence Awardee (2015)

Contact: Mr. Ronald Sara - 09157595258

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Node.is

React

Database

Photoshop

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Fabric of my life (03/2019 - 06/2019) 🗗

Exess Luggage (08/2018 – 09/2018) 🗹

Quote Generator (08/2019 – 08/2019) 🗹

This is a Quote generator app that will definitely give you the
encouragement you need in whatever it is that you may be going
through in your job, personal relationships or basically in life. You
also have the opportunity to share the quotes to Twitter if you wish
to. I hope this lightens up your day. :D

ORGANIZATIONS

Hack your Future - Copenhagen (09/2018 – Present)

CERTIFICATES

Hack Your Future (09/2018 – 06/2019)

LANGUAGES

English

Filipino

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Dansk

Norsk

Limited Working Proficiency

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Volleyball

Basketball

Badminton

Adventure

Travelling

Music

Photography